[Get 15%, 20% or 30% discount on our plans just for black friday, chat now and stay safe

Get 15%, 20% or 30% discount on our plans just for black friday, chat now and stay safe

Get 15%, 20% or 30% discount on our plans just for black friday, chat now and stay safe

Get 15%, 20% or 30% discount on our plans just for black friday, chat now and stay safe

Get 15%, 20% or 30% discount on our plans just for black friday, chat now and stay safe

Get 15%, 20% or 30% discount on our plans just for black friday, chat now and stay safe

](https://sucuri.net/live-chat/)

Menu

New Customer?

Privacy Policy
==============

Last Revised: November 30th, 2023

To view our archived Privacy Policy, [click here](https://sucuri.net/archived-privacy-policy/).

### Sucuri Global Privacy Notice

Sucuri products and services are offered through GoDaddy Media Temple, Inc. d/b/a Sucuri (“Sucuri”).  GoDaddy Media Temple, Inc. is a GoDaddy company, and GoDaddy’s Global Privacy Notice and the following related policies and procedures apply to Sucuri’s processing of Personal Data: 

* [European Privacy Notice Supplement for EU/EEA, Switzerland, and UK](https://www.godaddy.com/legal/agreements/european-supplemental-privacy-notice)

Please click on the hyperlinks above to review the applicable notices and supplements. 

### Exercising Your Privacy Rights

To exercise your privacy rights relating to processing of Personal Data by Sucuri, you can email us at [privacy@sucuri.net](mailto:privacy@sucuri.net) or by mail at the addresses listed below.  To exercise your privacy rights relating to other GoDaddy companies and products, you also can exercise your privacy rights as described in GoDaddy’s Global Privacy Notice and related documents linked above. 

### Contact Us

If you have any questions, you can contact us at [privacy@sucuri.net](mailto:privacy@surcuri.net) or by mail at: 

* United States: Attn: Office of the Data Privacy Officer, 2155 E. GoDaddy Way, Tempe, AZ 85284 USA 
* United Kingdom: Attn: Legal, Office of the Data Privacy Officer, 5th Floor, The Shipping Building, Old Vinyl Factory, 252-254 Blyth Road, Hayes, UB3 1HA. 
* European Union (EEA) / Switzerland: Attn: Legal, Office of the Data Privacy Officer, Sucuri c/o WeWork, Friesenplatz 4, 50672 Köln, Germany 
* Asia: Attn: Office of the Data Privacy Officer, 80 Robinson Road #02-00 Singapore 068898.

We respond to all questions or concerns within 30 days. 

Let’s Connect

© 2024 GoDaddy Mediatemple, Inc., d/b/a Sucuri. All rights reserved.

X

Sucuri Cookie Policy  

Our website uses cookies, which help us to improve our site and enables us to deliver the best possible service and customer experience.

Accept Decline Manage Options
